The Primary Source UP030
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Primary Source, 1982 -- 2012; UP030.001; 2.0 Linear Feet; 5 Volumes; 231 Digital Object(s)
  - 2007 Spring and 2007-2008 Academic Year, UP030.026.001
    - Primary Source, February 28, 2007; UP030.026.008.00036 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      25, 10
    - Primary Source, March 14, 2007; UP030.026.008.00037 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      XXV, 11
    - Primary Source May 20, 2007; UP030.026.008.00038 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      XXIV, 13
    - Primary Source, September 19, 2007; UP030.026.008.00039 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      26, 2
    - Primary Source, October 22, 2007; UP030.026.008.00040 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      XXVI, 4
    - Primary Source, January 30, 2008; UP030.026.008.00041 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      XXVI, 7
      Publications
    - Primary Source, February 27, 2008; UP030.026.008.00042 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      XXVI, 9
      Publications; publication
    - Primary Source, April 3, 2008; UP030.026.008.00043 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
    - Primary Source, April 16, 2008; UP030.026.008.00044 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      XXVI, 11
    - Primary Source, May 18, 2008; UP030.026.008.00045 (Volume UP030 Shared 8)
      XXVI, 12
  - 2008-2009 Academic Year, UP030.027.001
    - Primary Source, 2008-08-27; UP030.027.009.00001 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 1
    - Primary Source, 2008-09-27; UP030.027.009.00002 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 2
    - Primary Source, 2008-10-09; UP030.027.009.00003 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 3
    - Primary Source, 2008-10-29; UP030.027.009.00004 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 4
    - Primary Source, 2008-11-19; UP030.027.009.00005 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      Issue number is misprinted as issue 4. This should be issue 5.
      XXVII, 5
    - Primary Source, 2008-12-10; UP030.027.009.00006 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 6
    - Primary Source, 2009-01-28; UP030.027.009.00007 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 7
    - Primary Source, 2009-02-11; UP030.027.009.00008 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 8
    - Primary Source, 2009-02-25; UP030.027.009.00009 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 9
    - Primary Source, 2009-03-11; UP030.027.009.00010 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 10
    - Primary Source, 2009-04-01; UP030.027.009.00011 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 11
    - Primary Source, 2009-05-17; UP030.027.009.00012 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      Commencement Issue.
      XXVII, 12
  - 2009-2010 Academic Year, UP030.028.001
    - Primary Source, 2009-09-02; UP030.028.009.00013 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      Volume and series numbers reset during this group.
      XXVIII, 1
    - Primary Source, 2009-09-30; UP030.028.009.00014 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
    - Primary Source, 2009-10-21; UP030.028.009.00015 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
    - Primary Source, 2009-11-18; UP030.028.009.00016 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
    - Primary Source, 2009-12-16; UP030.028.009.00017 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 13
    - Primary Source, 2010-02-03; UP030.028.009.00018 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 14
    - Primary Source, 2010-02-24; UP030.028.009.00019 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 15
    - Primary Source, 2010-03-17; UP030.028.009.00020 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 16
    - Primary Source, 2010-04-07; UP030.028.009.00021 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 17
    - Primary Source, 2010-04-21; UP030.028.009.00022 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVII, 18
  - 2010-2011 Academic Year, UP030.029.001
    - Primary Source, 2010-09-03; UP030.029.009.00023 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
    - Primary Source, 2010-10-06; UP030.029.009.00024 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIII, 2
    - Primary Source, 2010-10-20; UP030.029.009.00025 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIII, 3
    - Primary Source, 2011-02-16; UP030.029.009.00026 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      Missing Issue 4.
      XXVIII, 5
    - Primary Source, 2011-03-02; UP030.029.009.00027 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIII, 6
    - Primary Source, 2011-03-30; UP030.029.009.00028 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIII, 7
    - Primary Source, 2011-04-20; UP030.029.009.00029 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIII, 8
    - Primary Source, 2011-05-22; UP030.029.009.00030 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      Commencement Issue. Volume and issue numbering is incorrect.
  - 2011-2012 Academic Year, UP030.030.001
    - Primary Source, 2011-09-28; UP030.030.009.00032 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      Volume should be XXIX.
      XXVIV, 2
    - Primary Source, 2011-10-12; UP030.030.009.00033 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIV, 3
    - Primary Source, 2011-10-26; UP030.030.009.00034 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIV, 4
    - Primary Source, 2011-11-16; UP030.030.009.00035 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIV, 5
    - Primary Source, 2011-12-14; UP030.030.009.00036 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIV, 6
    - Primary Source, 2012-02-01; UP030.030.009.00037 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIV, 7
    - Primary Source, 2012-02-29; UP030.030.009.00038 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIV, 8
    - Primary Source, 2012-03-14; UP030.030.009.00039 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIV, 9
    - Primary Source, 2012-04-04; UP030.030.009.00040 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXVIV, 10
    - Primary Source, 2012-05-02; UP030.030.009.00041 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXIX, 11
  - 2012-2013 Academic Year, UP030.031.001
    The Primary Source voluntarily ceased publication for Spring 2013 due to controversy caused by the December 12, 2013 issue.
    - Primary Source, 2012-09-12; UP030.031.009.00042 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      XXX, 1
    - Primary Source, 2012-12-12; UP030.031.009.00043 (Box UP030 Shared 9)
      Issue 2 is missing.
      XXX, 3